sitepen.com 2012-11-13

# Privacy Policy | SitePen

## Our legal team makes us do this…

SitePen, Inc. (“SitePen”, “we,” “us,” or “our”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of users of our products, services and web sites, such as http://sitepen.com (including each subdomain, the “Site”) and our software support services (the “Services”). We created this Privacy Policy to give you confidence and describe how we treat personal information as you visit and use our Site and Services. 

See our Contact page to contact us.

### Collection of Personal Information

We collect information from users including, for the Site, email address; user name; password; links, tags, comments, and any other information, data, text, software, music, audio, photographs, graphics, video, messages and other materials (“Content”) submitted by the user; log file information (such as IP address and browser data); and cookies. For the Services, we collect information including email address; user name; password; phone number; individual and entity names and addresses for persons obtaining the Services; Content regarding the user’s support issues or services needed; and payment/credit card information. 

Registration data. An email address, username and password are required for users to register on the Site. 

Content and other submissions. If you choose to submit Content on the Site, we will collect that information. We may examine it to provide better service and filter out any objectionable Content. We also collect Content you submit in connection with the Services, as well as information otherwise volunteered by users of our Site, such as by emailing or mailing us. 

Log file information. When users visit our Site, our servers automatically collect certain information that the browser sends when visiting Web sites in general. This log file information may include the URLs you visited; your IP address; date, time, and time spent on pages visited; and information about your browser and platform. 

Cookies. From time to time, our Site may use the “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your use of the same. We do not set any personally identifiable information in cookies. Cookies help us learn which portions of our Site are useful and which need improvement, among other things. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience with the Site may be significantly diminished and various features may not operate. 

### Use of Personal Information

Generally. We use the personally identifiable information and aggregate information we collect to maintain your account and market and provide the Site, the Services and our other products and services to you, to improve our offerings and to create new offerings, as provided below. Content and associated data submitted by users may be redisplayed to the public on public and private areas of the Site, except that Content and associated data submitted in connection with Services will be used only per the relevant Services agreement. 

Registration data. You may receive marketing communications from time to time. Each communication will provide you with ability to opt out of all future marketing correspondence. We may send you certain service and administrative notices regarding your purchased services, which are not subject to opt out. 

Log file information and cookies. We use cookies and log file information to remember your information so that you do not need to re-enter it when using the Site or the Services, to provide personalized Content; and to administer and monitor usage of the Site and the Services. 

Aggregate Information. We may use aggregate, non-personally-identifiable data to analyze usage of the Site and the Services and customize the Site’s content and layout, and to develop and provide our offerings. These uses improve our offerings and better tailor them to meet your needs. 

### Information Sharing

As a matter of policy, we do not sell, rent or otherwise share any of your personal information with third parties without your explicit consent. However, the following describes some of the ways that your personal information may be disclosed in the normal scope of business to provide the Site and the Services: We may share such information if we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to: (a) comply with any law, regulation or order, such as subpoena, court order or search warrant; (b) provide the Site and the Services using subcontractors under confidentiality agreement; (c) ensure compliance with our agreements, terms of use and policies; (d) protect and defend our rights or property, including investigations and defense of third-party claims; and/or (e) protect the rights, property and personal safety of our users, staff or the public. We reserve the right, in the event all or any relevant portion of our stock, business or assets is transferred to, acquired by or merged with any third party, to transfer or assign as part of such transaction any or all of the information we have collected. 

Content and associated data you submit may be displayed in public and private areas of the Site, except that Content and associated data submitted in connection with Services will be used only per the relevant Services agreement. 

We aggregate (gather up data across multiple user accounts) personal information and disclose such information in a non-personally identifiable manner to third parties for their analytical, development, marketing and promotional purposes. However, in these situations, we do not disclose to these entities any information that could be used to identify you personally. 

### Account Corrections

You may change your account settings by contacting us. However, we may retain any information to the extent required by law or otherwise in connection with the permitted information sharing described above. 

### Links

The Site and Content on it may contain links to other sites and resources controlled by third parties. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of these other sites or resources, and you should consult the privacy statements of such other sites and resources. 

### Data Security

The Site and Services have security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration. 

### Changes

We may amend this Privacy Policy, including the use of your information for new, unanticipated purposes, at any time by posting a revised version on the Site, and/or sending information regarding the amendment to your email address in our records. You are responsible for regularly reviewing the Site to obtain timely notice of such amendments. You shall be deemed to have accepted such amendments by continuing to use the Site and/or the Services after such amendments have been posted or information regarding such amendments has been sent to you. If you do not agree with any of such changes, you may immediately cease all access and use of the Site and/or the Services. You agree that such termination will be your exclusive remedy in such event. 

### International Users

The Site is hosted and the Services are provided in the United States of America. If you are accessing the Site or Services from the European Union, Asia, or any other jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure, which differ from United States laws, please be advised that through your use of the Site and the Services, you are transferring your personal information to the United States of America and you consent to that transfer. 

Effective date of this version: December 12, 2007
